<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Insider Tips For Consumers</title><link href="http://blog.consumernotebook.com" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://blog.consumernotebook.com/feeds/Consumer%20Notebook.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://blog.consumernotebook.com</id><updated>2012-02-22T17:11:00Z</updated><entry><title>Comparison: Over The Counter Allergy Medications</title><link href="http://blog.consumernotebook.com/comparison-over-the-counter-allergy-medications.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2012-02-22T17:11:00Z</updated><author><name>Audrey Roy</name></author><id>tag:blog.consumernotebook.com,2012-02-22:/comparison-over-the-counter-allergy-medications.html/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Here's a comparison I made of the leading OTC allergy medications available as of February 2012:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote class="pull-quote"&gt;
&lt;a class="reference external" href="http://consumernotebook.com/grids/audreyr/allergy-medication-face-off/"&gt;Allergy Medication Face-Off&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="which-should-you-choose"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Which should you choose?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since I'm not a doctor, I'm not allowed give you medical advice.  Ask your doctor, especially if what you're currently taking isn't working well enough for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</summary><category term="Consumer Notebook"></category></entry><entry><title>How To Buy Vinyl Banners</title><link href="http://blog.consumernotebook.com/how-to-buy-vinyl-banners.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2012-02-22T17:11:00Z</updated><author><name>Audrey Roy</name></author><id>tag:blog.consumernotebook.com,2012-02-22:/how-to-buy-vinyl-banners.html/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ordering vinyl banners can be kind of intimidating.  Here's a handy guide that walks you through the process:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol class="arabic simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Find out the size of the table, booth, or awning where the banner will hang.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the banners are for a trade show or conference, check the event website to see what size the booths and tables will be.  Contact the organizers if there's nothing on the website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the banners are for an awning, business, fence, or other physical location, go and measure the area where the banner will hang.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not sure of sizes?  Go with a 6-foot or 8-foot banner with a height of 2-3 feet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol class="arabic simple" start="2"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Poke around online until you find a cheap place to order banners of the size you want.  The best deals I could find today were:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul class="simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$12 for 2'x5' and $28 for 3'x8' color vinyl banners, BannersOnTheCheap - &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://bannersonthecheap.com"&gt;http://bannersonthecheap.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$6.99 for 3'x2' color vinyl banners, Banner Buzz - &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://bannerbuzz.com"&gt;http://bannerbuzz.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol class="arabic simple" start="3"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use the online design tools to put together your banner graphic.  Choose a color combination that stands out.  Here are the most useful signage design tips I found:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul class="simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If your vinyl banner will be hung outdoors: &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://www.primeoutdoor.co.za/outdoor-design-guidelines.php"&gt;http://www.primeoutdoor.co.za/outdoor-design-guidelines.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Color contrasts, from most to least visible: &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://www.outdoorfirst.com/ColorContrasts.aspx"&gt;http://www.outdoorfirst.com/ColorContrasts.aspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol class="arabic simple" start="4"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Order your banners!  Keep in mind that the first printing often has mistakes, so allow enough time for you to order a second print run if needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If your banner will be hanging from posts, a chainlink fence, or mounted to a building, you'll want to choose to have it grommetted during the order process.  The online shop should give you that option; if not, look at other shops.  You can then get zip ties at the hardware store to mount your banner through the grommets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol class="arabic simple" start="5"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you don't have a place to mount your banner, order a banner stand.  Indoor stands tend to be more polished-looking, while outdoor stands have a more rugged appearance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're not sure where your banner will go, choose an outdoor stand.  Outdoor stands usually have a weighted base that can be filled with sand or water, to keep your banner from falling down in the wind.&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><category term="Consumer Notebook"></category></entry><entry><title>Welcome</title><link href="http://blog.consumernotebook.com/welcome.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2012-02-22T09:41:00Z</updated><author><name>Audrey Roy</name></author><id>tag:blog.consumernotebook.com,2012-02-22:/welcome.html/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello! We're the team behind &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://consumernotebook.com"&gt;Consumer Notebook&lt;/a&gt;.  We're starting this collection of consumer tips because we know a lot of little tidbits that we think will be useful to others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep watching for updates from &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://audreymroy.com"&gt;Audrey Roy&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://pydanny.com"&gt;Daniel Greenfeld&lt;/a&gt;.  Don't forget to bookmark this site and add it to your newsfeed readers.&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><category term="Consumer Notebook"></category></entry></feed>