<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Insider Tips For Consumers</title><link href="http://blog.consumernotebook.com" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://blog.consumernotebook.com/feeds/Consumer%20Notebook.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://blog.consumernotebook.com</id><updated>2012-02-23T20:40:00Z</updated><entry><title>Comparison: 8 Books That Will Teach You Python Programming</title><link href="http://blog.consumernotebook.com/comparison-8-books-that-will-teach-you-python-programming.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2012-02-23T20:40:00Z</updated><author><name>Daniel Greenfeld</name></author><id>tag:blog.consumernotebook.com,2012-02-23:/comparison-8-books-that-will-teach-you-python-programming.html/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Want a a career that promises work for the rest of your life? Then become a software developer. In order to do that, you need to learn a language. My language preference is Python. Python is easy to pick up and yet powerful enough to have been chosen by Google, NASA, and other organizations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to learn Python, here are some good resources:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote class="pull-quote"&gt;
&lt;a class="reference external" href="http://consumernotebook.com/grids/pydanny/python-books-for-beginners/"&gt;Python books for beginners&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These books are great for getting started, but you have to do the work. It takes time and a lot of hard work to get to the point where you are ready to become a software developer. If you stick with working on projects and always finding ways to program things, you'll eventually get to the point where these books become a fond memory of your early days of a Python developer, and you'll start looking for higher level resources.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you've mastered Python, or at least gotten the hang of things, here are some favorite Python programming books meant for more experienced developers:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote class="pull-quote"&gt;
&lt;a class="reference external" href="http://consumernotebook.com/grids/pydanny/must-have-python-programming-books/"&gt;Must-Have Python Programming Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These are my go-to references as a professional software developer. I have both PDF and paper versions of them. They provide answers to sophisticated questions, and make great reading on long trips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are a lot more Python books then what I've listed here. There are books on Web Development,  Check out the growing compilation of Python books I've assembled at &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://consumernotebook.com/lists/pydanny/complete-list-of-python-programming-books/"&gt;The Complete List of Python Programming books&lt;/a&gt;. If something isn't here, contact me on &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://twitter.com/pydanny`"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; and let me know!&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><category term="Consumer Notebook"></category></entry><entry><title>Comparison: Over The Counter Allergy Medications</title><link href="http://blog.consumernotebook.com/comparison-over-the-counter-allergy-medications.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2012-02-22T17:11:00Z</updated><author><name>Audrey Roy</name></author><id>tag:blog.consumernotebook.com,2012-02-22:/comparison-over-the-counter-allergy-medications.html/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Here's a comparison I made of the leading OTC allergy medications available as of February 2012:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(widget goes here)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="which-should-you-choose"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Which should you choose?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since I'm not a doctor, I'm not allowed give you medical advice.  Ask your doctor, especially if what you're currently taking isn't working well enough for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</summary><category term="Consumer Notebook"></category></entry><entry><title>How To Buy Vinyl Banners</title><link href="http://blog.consumernotebook.com/how-to-buy-vinyl-banners.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2012-02-22T17:11:00Z</updated><author><name>Audrey Roy</name></author><id>tag:blog.consumernotebook.com,2012-02-22:/how-to-buy-vinyl-banners.html/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ordering vinyl banners can be kind of intimidating.  Here's what you do:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol class="arabic simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Find out the size of the table, booth, or awning where the banner will hang.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the banners are for a trade show or conference, check the event website to see what size the booths and tables will be.  Contact the organizers if there's nothing on the website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the banners are for an awning, business, fence, or other physical location, go and measure the area where the banner will hang.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not sure of sizes?  Go with a 6-foot or 8-foot banner with a height of 2-3 feet.&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><category term="Consumer Notebook"></category></entry><entry><title>Welcome</title><link href="http://blog.consumernotebook.com/welcome.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2012-02-22T09:41:00Z</updated><author><name>Audrey Roy</name></author><id>tag:blog.consumernotebook.com,2012-02-22:/welcome.html/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello! We're the team behind &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://consumernotebook.com"&gt;Consumer Notebook&lt;/a&gt;.  We're starting this collection of consumer tips because we know a lot of little tidbits that we think will be useful to others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep watching for updates from &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://audreymroy.com"&gt;Audrey Roy&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://pydanny.com"&gt;Daniel Greenfeld&lt;/a&gt;.  Don't forget to bookmark this site and add it to your newsfeed readers.&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><category term="Consumer Notebook"></category></entry></feed>